/*--- QUIZ OBJECTS ---*/

//easyQuiz

var easyQuestions = [
	{
		question: 'The 1984 film \'Amadeus\' was based off of the life of which famous composer?',
		correctAnswer: 'Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart',
		incorrectAnswers: ['John Cage', 'Karl Amadeus Hartmann', 'Igor Stravinsky'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},
	
	{
		question: 'Which composer wrote the film scores for \'Star Wars\', \'Jurassic Park\', and \'Indiana Jones\'?',
		correctAnswer: 'John Williams',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Hans Zimmer', 'Howard Shore', 'Michael Giacchino'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},

	{
		question: 'Which composer is well known for his ballets, the most famous ones being \'The Nutcracker\' and \'Swan Lake\'?',
		correctAnswer: 'Pyotr Ilych Tchaikovsky',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Joseph Haydn', 'Edward Elgar', 'Franz Liszt'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},
	
	{
		question: 'Which famous composer was deaf?',
		correctAnswer: 'Ludwig Von Beethoven',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart', 'Johann Sebastian Bach', 'Frederic Chopin'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},

	{
		question: 'Which composer is best known for his \'Hallelujah Chorus\'? (Hint: it\'s most often performed at Christmastime)',
		correctAnswer: 'George Frideric Handel',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Sergei Rachmaninov', 'Gustav Mahler', 'Felix Medlessohn'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},		
];

var hardQuestions = [

	{
		question: 'What was Hildegard von Bingen\'s favorite color?',
		correctAnswer: 'Green',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Red', 'Yellow', 'Blue'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},

	{
		question: 'Which composer was an obsessive perfectionist that he regularly synchronized all of the clocks in his apartment?',
		correctAnswer: 'Dmitri Shostakovich',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Antonio Vivaldi, Ludwig von Beethoven', 'Gustav Mahler'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},

	{
		question: 'Which composer is well known for his piece 4\'33", in which the performer sits siilently for 4 minutes and 33 seconds?',
		correctAnswer: 'John Cage',
		incorrectAnswers: ['Anton Webern', 'Arnold Schoenberg', 'Edward Elgar'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},

	{
		question: 'Which composer was the father of 20 children?',
		correctAnswer: 'Johann Sebastian Bach',
		incorrectAnswers: ['George Gershwin'. 'Gustav Mahler', 'Johann Strauss'],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},

	{
		question: 'Which composer died of a chill after coming home from the pub one night only to find that his wife had locked him out?',
		correctAnswer: '',
		incorrectAnswers: [],
		answerInfo: '',
		answerPicture: '',
	},
];

